

Student for Industrial Engineering and Management at Ben Gurion University with specialization in information systems.

Analytical thinker, tech enthusiast, highly motivated, creative and a team player. **Interested** in a creative, innovative and challenging work environment in the world of information systems, data analytics and visualization.

Amit Kapon

Phone:

0547668803

E-Mail:

Amitkapon@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/amit-kapon-7818421b2/

Technical knowledge

- SQL
- HTML, CSS, JS
- RStudio
- Java
- Microsoft BI
- VBA
- C#
- LabView

Languages

Hebrew English

Experience

2018-Present: Exercise Analyst, Eltel Technologistics Ltd:

- Responsible for analyzing the exercise and publishing learning materials according to the client requirements.
- Took part in **training new employees** on the information system.
- Took part in the implementation of a new information system for the analyst department - provided reviews and adjustments required from off-the-shelf software, SAT and more.

Military service

2014-2015:

- Divisional Safety and Knowledge Management Officer, responsible for knowledge retention and arrangement as well as for safety in variety of fields – Samaria regional division.
- Initiated a project to build new divisional website to preserve operational knowledge.

2011-2014:

- Combat service as a commander and officer.
- Training soldiers to be commanders "Bislah 17" Commander school.
- Leading a platoon in training and operations Kfir division.

Education

• 3rd year for B.Sc. in Industrial Engineering and Management at Ben Gurion University.

Community

 Took part in "Perach" scholarship with the Ethiopian community in Beer Sheva, to strengthen and promote the Ethiopian youth.